LIOR DILER

Full Stack Developer











My 5 years of studying and professional experience has allowed programming to become my

With a wide variety of experience in different fields such as Frontend, Backend and Video Game Development, I have aquired the skill to adapt and learn new technologies.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: C#, C++, C, Java, Javascript, Python, Android

Database: SQL, MongoDB

Systems: Linux, Windows, Android, MacOS

Frameworks: Node.js, React, Express, Nginx, OpenGL, Shader

Tools: Docker, Github, Gitlab, Unity, Unreal Engine, Blender, Houdini

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCES

Full Stack Developer

Inria | October 2019 - August 2022

Technical Environment: Linux, Docker, NodeJS, React, MongoDB, Gitlab-ci, Nginx

- Software architecture design
- Application development (Backend and Frontend)
- Unit testing
- · Automatic deployment
- · Application security management
- Automatic documentation generation

R&D Developer in Robotics

Teamnet | June 2017 - August 2019

Technical Environment: Java Spring, Linux, MYSQL, Git, Jenkins, Sonar

- Creation of a linguistic Chatbot
- Development of the backend (API, program, database...)
- Setting up Docker
- Database management

PROJECTS

Contribution to the SIGGRAPH research competition, Rollback Hybrid Netcode (C++, C#)

Creation of courses on immersion in Virtual Reality with Binaural Audio (C#, C)

Implementation of a Machine Learning Library (C++)

Genetic Algorithm for Procedural Animation (C#, Python, Unity, Blender)

Artificial Intelligence for Video Games (C#, C++)

Image Processing Applications (C++, openCV)

Ray-tracing Engine (C++)

2D Game Engine (C++)

Compute Shader for Particle Generation (C#, Shader)

Development of a Real-time Strategy Game (C#, Unity)

Development of a Pathfinding Game (C++, Unreal Engine)

Generation of Bézier Curves (C#, Unity)

Procedural Rendering (WebGL, Blender)

EDUCATION

Master's degree in software and network project management

ESGI Paris 2020 - 2022

Bachelor's degree in software and network project management

ESGI Paris 2019 - 2020

Advanced technician's diploma in IT

CFA Insta 2017 - 2019

High school diploma in **Laboratory Sciences**

Lycée Ecole Technique Supérieur du Laboratoire 2016 - 2017

I TRAITS

Self-motivated

Curious

Serious

Passionate

LANGUAGES

French (Native language)

English (Native language)

Turkish (Fluent)

INTERESTS

Music

Travelling

Video game competitions

